

#### **SUMMARY**

Software development and management engineering graduate passionate about systems and constant learning of programming languages.

I bring a positive attitude and motivation to learn more and improve myself, as well as constant support and optimization in teamwork.

Technologically and socially savvy, I offer experience with many social media platforms, office software, and basic and intermediate IT skills

### PERSONAL INFORMATION



+52 1 81 2441 0896



salinasreynalazaro@gmail.com



Lázaro Daniel Salinas Reyna



Bosque de Jacaranda 110, Bosques de San Miguel, Apodaca, Nuevo León, México, C.P. 66647

### **CORE SKILLS**

- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft .NET & C#
- HTML5 & CS3
- Angular
- Java
- Database Administration
- Use of Operating Systems
- Linux

# LÁZARO DANIEL SALINAS REYNA

Industry 4.0 Intern

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Conductores Monterrey (Viakable) – Industry 4.0 Intern February 2023 – Present

Experience in both back-end and front-end web applications development and IoT Software in an industrial environment, usage of SQL Server to save and read data in real time mainly using Microsoft Software Development (.NET, C#, Blazor, SQL Server etc.)

## Majorel – Customer Service Representative. August 2021 – April 2022

Training and experience in the reporting process in relation to support and customer service from Majorel attending calls and answering message form social media and ticket creation and management.

### **EDUCATION**

Universidad Tecnológica Gral. Mariano Escobedo – Ciudad General Escobedo 2022 – 2024

Bachelor's Degree in Software Development and Management Engineering.

Universidad Tecnológica Gral. Mariano Escobedo – Ciudad General Escobedo 2019 – 2022

Higher Technical University Degree in IT – Multiplatform Software Development.

### CBTIS #53 - Ciudad Apodaca

2016 - 2019

Technical Degree in Programming.

## **SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Responsible
- Bilingual
- Adaptable
- Communication
- Problem solving
- Decision Making
- Teamwork